[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All tigers have stripes.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1939 movie was the last American-made movie shown in Nazi-occupied France.", "correct_answer": "Mr. Smith Goes to Washington", "incorrect_answers": ["The Wizard of Oz", "Gone With the Wind", "King Kong"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the term iIkizukuri which is used in Japanese cuisine?", "correct_answer": "Prepared alive", "incorrect_answers": ["Seafood", "Deep fried", "Brewed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which company demonstrated the first GPRS mobile phone with video-on-demand in March of 2002?", "correct_answer": "Samsung", "incorrect_answers": ["Sony Ericsson", "Motorola", "Nokia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1980 William Friedkin released Cruising, a controversial movie about a serial killer who targets gay men during the 1970s. What actor starred as Officer Steve Burns in this movie?", "correct_answer": "Al Pacino", "incorrect_answers": ["Dustin Hoffman", "Richard Gere", "Robert DeNiro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pigeons are only one of seven species to pass the mirror test, which tests if animals recognize their own reflected image.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Great Lion who is a central character in C. S. Lewis series of fantasy novels The Chronicles of Narnia?", "correct_answer": "Aslan", "incorrect_answers": ["Saraf", "Sarabi", "Sabor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is the largest nocturnal prosimian on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Aye-aye", "incorrect_answers": ["Gorilla", "Mantled Guereza", "Olive Baboon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who said Huh? Sorry in the film The Goonies?", "correct_answer": "Brand", "incorrect_answers": ["Data", "Mikey", "Mouth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is something specific about Anne Boleyns ghost. What is it?", "correct_answer": "Her ghost is without a head.", "incorrect_answers": ["She does not have a ghost.", "Her ghost is male.", "Her ghost is without hands."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest river on the planet by volume?", "correct_answer": "The Amazon", "incorrect_answers": ["The Mississippi", "The Nile", "The Ganges"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following dialogue is from the movie Star Trek IV - The Voyage Home.   \nKirk: Oh, him? (referring to Spock ) I think he did a little too much LDS.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]